123franchising.net 2012-08-05

# Privacy Policy

At 123 Franchising Inc, we are committed to protecting your privacy.  This privacy policy relates to the use of any personal information you provide to us through 123franchising.net.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions during registration or the sending of an enquiry, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

**Personal Information**  
You can view all of the content on our website without providing any personal information what so ever. However, if you wish to seek additional information regarding a franchise opportunity, your personal details will be requested to complete an enquiry.

The information you submit via our enquiry forms are only shared with the companies that you request information from.  
123franchising.net does not share, sell or trade your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes, unless authorised by you, however our USA sales representatives may contact you from time to time with any relevant offers or opportunities, via telephone or emails.

**Submit Your Enquiry Form**  
When you submit an enquiry form for more information from one of our listed franchises, your contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail, etc.) on the enquiry form, will be passed only to the franchise business that you specify. No other franchise or business receives your contact information. Your information, however, is often stored in the receiving company’s database, as well as ours. Collected data may be stored outside the USA.

**Cookies**  
We may collect non-personal information from your computer using cookies.  We use the collected information for site, analytical and marketing purposes.  It is not linked to any of your personal information.

In order to provide you with a better experience on 123franchising.net, we ask that you do not set your browser to reject cookies.

**Testimonials**  
Customer testimonials are often posted on our website which may contain personally identifiable information such as a franchisees or suppliers name and location.  However, we always obtain the franchisors consent prior to posting the testimonial, and assume that the franchisor/ client, has the authority to allow us to use this information. 

**Newsletter**  
You will only be added to our newsletter mailing list if you register to receive it. Your personal information will never be shared with any third parties. If you wish to unsubscribe from the mailing list, you may opt out by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link on our emails or alternatively email [usa@123franchising.net](mailto:usa@123franchising.net?subject=Newletter%20Opt%20Out).  
**  
Links to other sites**  
We may provide links to other companies from our site. Once you leave and enter another website, whether within or outside the USA, you are subject to their privacy policies, and therefore we advise you to review their privacy policies before use.

**Children's Privacy**  
123 Franchising Inc is intended to be used by individuals over the age of 18. We do not seek or willingly collect information on children under the age of 18. If we discover that we have collected information of an individual under the age of 18, then we will remove that information from our system and the information will be permanently deleted. 

**Security**  
While no data transfer can be 100% secure, 123 Franchising Inc will make reasonable efforts to secure your personal data while being transferred, stored or processed. We also use strict procedures within our organisation to ensure that all personal data are kept secure. All 123 Franchising Websites across the world are subject to the same security policies and procedures.

**Updated Privacy Policy**  
123 Franchising Inc reserves the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy at any time. Any modifications, additions or deletions shall be made effective, as soon as it is posted on the website, unless otherwise indicated. We encourage you to check back regularly and review this privacy policy.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personal identifiable information as required by US Federal & State Law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding or a court order of a USA Court of Law.
